itradecimb.com.my 2011-12-09

# i*Trade@CIMB MY

Maintaining our clients' trust is critical to our success. We believe in the importance of safeguarding our clients' information while seeking to deliver premium financial solutions.  
  
  * CIMB may collect personal information arising out of your use of this website. The use of information collected is governed by this privacy policy and, where applicable, any agreement you may have with CIMB or its subsidiaries.

  * CIMB will treat such personal information as confidential and will limit its use and retention for the purposes of our services to you and to facilitate your use of this website.

  * CIMB may share such personal information with its affiliates. In so doing CIMB will adhere to all applicable laws, regulations, rules and industry standards. If CIMB engages an unaffiliated company or service provider to assist in the provision of financial services, the use of your personal information will be governed by a separate agreement relating to the provision of those services.

  * CIMB or its affiliates may under certain circumstances be obliged to disclose your personal information to governmental, statutory or regulatory authorities.

 **Disclaimer of warranty and limitation of liability**  
The information provided on this website is provided without any expressed or implied warranty as to its completeness or accuracy. This is due to the fact that it is not possible for CIMB or its affiliates to have regard to your particular financial circumstances. Do not rely on any information or opinion contained in this website without prior consultation with a duly authorised representative of CIMB or its affiliate.

CIMB assumes no liability should you suffer loss in reliance of any such information or opinion other than liability under statute that cannot be excluded.
